

Erlend Brodal

Game Developer

erlendbrodal@gmail.com



www.erlendbrodal.com



Dalslandsgade 8, C212, 2300 Copenhagen



I am a **technical artist**, currently living in Copenhagen. My specialties are shader development, procedural generation, and 3D. I have experience in creating custom tools for artists for software such as Unreal Engine and Unity. I mostly work with 3D Environments, both big and small, while organizing the whole art pipeline from Sketch to Build.

Work Experience

Technical Art Director at Sharp Raccoon, Trondheim August 2020 – Now

Co -founder of the company, working as the lead artist. My contribution is developing workflow and pipeline for 3D and shaders.

Software Developer at Way AS, Trondheim

June 2020 - 2020

Developing a Car Simulator for use in driving education.

Teacher Assistant at Nord Universitet, Trondheim

August 2018 - June 2019

Holding workshops and helping students with game development

Education

Master's in games, IT-University of Copenhagen August 2019 – July 2021

Bachelor' in Games and Entertainment Technology, Nord University August 2016 – July 2019